# livari Rantala, OUAS

Engineer Student, information and communication technologies

Juolavehnätie 1 C4 90580 Oulu 040 191 8686 rantalaiivari@gmail.com

#### **Profile**

Hi my name is livari, I am a 20- year old student from Oulu. I'm a first year student in information and communication technologies in Oulu university of applied sciences. As an employee I am very self-initiated, hard working and eager to learn new things. I have accumulated work experience from many fields since i was 14- years old. I also have a drivers license.



### **Experience**

## Veli Seppä OY

Helper, 2015 and 2019-2020

My job description in this company was wide: mowing the lawn, sanding, plow snow, maintenance of the company equipment and overall property maintenance.

#### **V8-Burger**

Shop Assistant, Summer 2017–2018

My job in this company included keeping the shop clean, making ice cream, sales and running everyday errands for the shop.

#### **SSAB** Raahe

Slab restorer, May 2021-Dec 2021, Mar 3rd 2022-Mar 29th 2022, May 2022-Aug 2022

I worked in this company as a stand-in, at the gas planer. My job included restoring steel slabs by hand or by machine for further refine. As an restorer by hand, my job was to detect errors in the slab and fix them. Additionally I kept every slab number in my notepad to avoid confusions. As an restorer by machine my job was to drive the slabs through the machine, after that the slabs went to the hand restorer. This job required being very precise and careful.

#### Education

#### Elementary school | 2009-2018

Honganpalo primary school and Saloinen upper comprehensive school, Raahe

# Higschool graduate | Aug 2018–Jun 2021

Pyhäjoki high school, Pyhäjoki

I went to high school in Pyhäjoki, where I got experience on making magazines and entrepreneurship, when I worked as an graphic designer for the Pyhäjoen Kuulumiset - magazine.

# Language skills

Finnish Native language
Swedish Mediocre
English Fluent

# **Hobbies**

Going to the gym, Playing videogames, photography, playing piano, ice hockey and football